
[
  {
    "question": "Which animal kills the most humans annually?",
    "options": ["Bee", "Shark", "Snake", "Mosquito"],
    "correctOption": 3,
    "points": 20
  },
  {
    "question": "According to scientists, an attack on a person by which of these animals is most likely to kill the person?",
    "options": ["Hippopotamus", "Grizzly Bear", "Shark", "Crocodile"],
    "correctOption": 0,
    "points": 10
  },
  {
    "question": "The stings of which creature kill hundreds of swimmers each year?",
    "options": ["Barracuda", "Jellyfish", "Squid", "Octopus"],
    "correctOption": 1,
    "points": 10
  },
  {
    "question": "Rabies, which kills about 59,000 people each year, is transmitted almost entirely by which animal?",
    "options": ["Rat", "Bat", "Raccoon", "Dog"],
    "correctOption": 3,
    "points": 10
  },
  {
    "question": "A delicacy in Japan, which fish has killed diners with its powerful toxin?",
    "options": [
      "Puffer Fish",
      "Bluefin Tuna",
      "Moray Eel",
      "Sea Snake"
    ],
    "correctOption": 0,
    "points": 10
  },
  {
    "question": "From 1979 to 2019, attacks by which animal killed the most people in the United State and Canada?",
    "options": ["Cougar", "Brown Bear", "Wolf", "Alligator"],
    "correctOption": 1,
    "points": 10
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of these animals has the strongest recorded jaw strength?",
    "options": [
      "Saltwater Crocodile",
      "Polar Bear",
      "Silverback Gorilla",
      "Spotted Hyena"
    ],
    "correctOption": 0,
    "points": 30
  },
  {
    "question": "To help prevent deadly encounters between elephants and human, farmers rely on which method to ward off elephants?",
    "options": [
      "Setting up elephant-shaped \"scarecrows\"",
      "Using flashing television screens",
      "Burning chili powder",
      "Using air horns"
    ],
    "correctOption": 2,
    "points": 20
  },
  {
    "question": "Accused of devouring more than 130 people, the \"man-eaters\" of Tsvao were a pair of what?",
    "options": [
      "Tigers",
      "Hyenas",
      "Crocodiles",
      "Lions"
    ],
    "correctOption": 3,
    "points": 30
  },
  {
    "question": "Helping to make deadly animals a little less deadly, antivenom is made by doing what?",
    "options": [
      "Pumping venomous animals full of antibiotics",
      "Mixing venom with powerful vitamins",
      "Injecting venom into animals to produce antibodies",
      "Boiling venom to remove its toxins"
    ],
    "correctOption": 2,
    "points": 30
  },
  {
    "question": "Which shark is often considered more dangerous to people than the great white, because it can swim in fresh water?",
    "options": ["Hammerhead Shark", "Bull Shark", "Thresher Shark", "Mako Shark"],
    "correctOption": 1,
    "points": 10
  },
  {
    "question": "The bite of which animal is roughly equivalent to a bee sting?",
    "options": [
      "Black Widow Spider",
      "Bark Scorpion",
      "Tarantula",
      "Recluse Spider"
    ],
    "correctOption": 2,
    "points": 30
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of these African animals is nicknamed \"Black Death\"?",
    "options": [
      "Black Spitting Cobra",
      "Cape Buffalo",
      "Black Panther",
      "Gorilla"
    ],
    "correctOption": 1,
    "points": 30
  },
  {
    "question": "One of the deadly snakes in the world, the Inland taipan is renowned for what?",
    "options": [
      "Having six-inch fangs",
      "Having extremely toxic venom",
      "Having unusual crushing power",
      "Measuring more than 30 feet long"
    ],
    "correctOption": 1,
    "points": 20
  },
  {
    "question": "Responsible for spreading a deadly disease, which creature is among the world's most lethal?",
    "options": [
      "Centipede",
      "Leech",
      "Lady Bug",
      "Snail"
    ],
    "correctOption": 3,
    "points": 30
  }
]